[{"answer": "Arthur, good to see you again.  Let me introduce my colleague to you.  This i", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Nice to meet you, Patsy.  Im Arthur Boglid", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Arthur, good to see you again.  Let me introduce my colleague to you.  This i", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Nice to finally meet you", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Nice to meet you, Patsy.  Im Arthur Boglid", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Would you like some coffee or tea", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Nice to finally meet you", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Coffee would be fine, thank you", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Would you like some coffee or tea", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " How was your flight", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Coffee would be fine, thank you", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " It was pretty good.  We had a little weather delay leaving Texas, but no othe", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 23, "question": " How was your flight", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Good, Im glad to hear it.  Well, why dont we get down to business", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 27, "question": " It was pretty good.  We had a little weather delay leaving Texas, but no othe", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " All right", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Good, Im glad to hear it.  Well, why dont we get down to business", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": "As we all know, were here today to talk about your requirements that need to b", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 32, "question": " All right", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Lets start off with your requirements, Arthur.  What salary level would yo", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 37, "question": "As we all know, were here today to talk about your requirements that need to b", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " I think $200,000 a year would be a fair salary that I could accept.  I cant leav", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Lets start off with your requirements, Arthur.  What salary level would yo", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Well, we could offer you $170,000", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 45, "question": " I think $200,000 a year would be a fair salary that I could accept.  I cant leav", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Id take $185,000", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Well, we could offer you $170,000", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Youre the best person for this position, Arthur.  So, were willing to make ", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Id take $185,000", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " I can agree to that.  I can pay my own relocation expenses if I get that salary i", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Youre the best person for this position, Arthur.  So, were willing to make ", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Great.  So were all in agreement that your annual salary will be $185,000.  D", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 56, "question": " I can agree to that.  I can pay my own relocation expenses if I get that salary i", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": "Yes, I do.  Id like an additional five days of vacation per year in addition to wha", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Great.  So were all in agreement that your annual salary will be $185,000.  D", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Im afraid vacation days are non-negotiable.  In fairness to all employees at th", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Yes, I do.  Id like an additional five days of vacation per year in addition to wha", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Thats unfortunate.  I have an excellent vacation policy at my current position", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Im afraid vacation days are non-negotiable.  In fairness to all employees at th", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Another benefit we can offer you is use of a company car of your choosing.  Th", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Thats unfortunate.  I have an excellent vacation policy at my current position", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Well, that would be a great benefit.  I guess Im willing to compromise on th", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Another benefit we can offer you is use of a company car of your choosing.  Th", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Excellent.  Do you have any other issues youd like to discuss", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Well, that would be a great benefit.  I guess Im willing to compromise on th", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " No, I dont think so.  I accept the position", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Excellent.  Do you have any other issues youd like to discuss", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Wonderful", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 79, "question": " No, I dont think so.  I accept the position", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Well, its a deal then.  Arthur, youll receive $185,000 a year and get the use of ", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Wonderful", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " I agree", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Well, its a deal then.  Arthur, youll receive $185,000 a year and get the use of ", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Well draw up a contract and then all of us here will need to sign it.  When are yo", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 88, "question": " I agree", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " On Friday", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Well draw up a contract and then all of us here will need to sign it.  When are yo", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Super.  Well get that contract done by tomorrow morning and then you can sign i", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 93, "question": " On Friday", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Sure.  Sounds good", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Super.  Well get that contract done by tomorrow morning and then you can sign i", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Welcome to the team, Arthur.  Were all looking forward to working with you", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Sure.  Sounds good", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " Thank you, Im looking forward to it too", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 99, "question": " Welcome to the team, Arthur.  Were all looking forward to working with you", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " Congratulations", "docId": "01-09", "aSentId": 100, "question": " Thank you, Im looking forward to it too", "qSentId": 99}]
